[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Why would it be a show?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "it", "be", "a", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, I don't -- that's what I want to know, because everybody's talking about it, that this is a show.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "that", "'s", "what", "I", "want", "to", "know", ",", "because", "everybody", "'s", "talking", "about", "it", ",", "that", "this", "is", "a", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "With all your expert knowledge of bomb making and bombs, is it likely that they could have pulled off this Boston marathon double bombing in the extremely efficient successful way that they did without having physically trained with similar devices, at least Tamerlan, back in somewhere like Dagestan?", "question_tokens": ["With", "all", "your", "expert", "knowledge", "of", "bomb", "making", "and", "bombs", ",", "is", "it", "likely", "that", "they", "could", "have", "pulled", "off", "this", "Boston", "marathon", "double", "bombing", "in", "the", "extremely", "efficient", "successful", "way", "that", "they", "did", "without", "having", "physically", "trained", "with", "similar", "devices", ",", "at", "least", "Tamerlan", ",", "back", "in", "somewhere", "like", "Dagestan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "JJS", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "ILLER: You know, Piers, it actually works either way.", "answer_tokens": ["ILLER", ":", "You", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "it", "actually", "works", "either", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston", "Dagestan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Are those not enough to trigger real alarm bells?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "those", "not", "enough", "to", "trigger", "real", "alarm", "bells", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, they're not really warnings.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "really", "warnings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "I'd be very curious to say, if he was a threat to the Russians, what did they do with him while he was on their turf?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'d", "be", "very", "curious", "to", "say", ",", "if", "he", "was", "a", "threat", "to", "the", "Russians", ",", "what", "did", "they", "do", "with", "him", "while", "he", "was", "on", "their", "turf", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "John, stay with me.", "answer_tokens": ["John", ",", "stay", "with", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Have we seen exactly the same thing happen again here?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "we", "seen", "exactly", "the", "same", "thing", "happen", "again", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Piers, I don't think anyone that I know of was foolish enough to give that sort of assurance.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "anyone", "that", "I", "know", "of", "was", "foolish", "enough", "to", "give", "that", "sort", "of", "assurance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Is that the new phase of the war on terror?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "new", "phase", "of", "the", "war", "on", "terror", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, I think it's a little early to say that al Qaeda is not part of the problem as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "little", "early", "to", "say", "that", "al", "Qaeda", "is", "not", "part", "of", "the", "problem", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Have we crossed that red line by that criteria, and if so, what should the president be doing about it?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "we", "crossed", "that", "red", "line", "by", "that", "criteria", ",", "and", "if", "so", ",", "what", "should", "the", "president", "be", "doing", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Well, it would appear that we have but it seems to me the red line should have been something much, much earlier.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "would", "appear", "that", "we", "have", "but", "it", "seems", "to", "me", "the", "red", "line", "should", "have", "been", "something", "much", ",", "much", "earlier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Or was there a duty of care, if you like, to an American citizen, as Dzhokhar is, to give him his Miranda rights at that time?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "was", "there", "a", "duty", "of", "care", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "to", "an", "American", "citizen", ",", "as", "Dzhokhar", "is", ",", "to", "give", "him", "his", "Miranda", "rights", "at", "that", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Well, I think you framed the argument there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "you", "framed", "the", "argument", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Well, he sounds so far like a charismatic recruiter.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "sounds", "so", "far", "like", "a", "charismatic", "recruiter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "How much of it is deserved?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "it", "is", "deserved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I think, you know, we have to trace it back, Piers, to say how did this whole thing start.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "have", "to", "trace", "it", "back", ",", "Piers", ",", "to", "say", "how", "did", "this", "whole", "thing", "start", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "I mean, her injuries were pretty serious?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "her", "injuries", "were", "pretty", "serious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Yeah, she was very serious.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "she", "was", "very", "serious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "What is your feeling towards them from what they've done to your fiance?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "feeling", "towards", "them", "from", "what", "they", "'ve", "done", "to", "your", "fiance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well, it's nuts.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "nuts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Aaron"]}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "First of all, how is Aaron, your little boy?", "question_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "how", "is", "Aaron", ",", "your", "little", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "You know, Aaron has made an amazing recovery, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Aaron", "has", "made", "an", "amazing", "recovery", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "What has been his reaction to the fact that somebody just turned up to bomb people?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "been", "his", "reaction", "to", "the", "fact", "that", "somebody", "just", "turned", "up", "to", "bomb", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "His reaction, it was one of -- it's been a lot of things.", "answer_tokens": ["His", "reaction", ",", "it", "was", "one", "of", "--", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "lot", "of", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "How did that go?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Oh, it was wonderful.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "was", "wonderful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]